你是星战银河系里的吗
Okay. Are you from the Star Wars universe?
是
Yes.
是原始三部曲里的吗
Were you in the original trilogy?
是
Yes.
是不是我钱包里 夹着一张你穿金属比基尼的照片
Oh, is there a picture of you in my wallet wearing a metal bikini?
老天  我可不希望如此
God, I hope not.
不对  不是莱娅公主
And no, I'm not Princess Leia.
轮到我了
Okay, okay. My turn. Um...
六部星战电影都有你吗
Are you in all six Star Wars movies?
-对  -有意思
- Yes. - Interesting.
你是机器人吗
Are you a droid?
是
Yes.
是不是有点像闪闪亮的谢尔顿
Do you kind of look like a shiny Sheldon?
是
Yes.
C-3PO
C-3PO.
猜对了
You got it.
太荒谬了
That's preposterous.
我才不像C-3PO呢
I do not resemble C-3PO.
别误会
Don't get me wrong.
虽然受宠若惊  但我不这么认为
I'm flattered. I just don't see it.
是莱斯利·温克尔
Leslie Winkle.
接通"互利友人"
You've reached "Friends with Benefits."
性爱电招  请按一
For a booty call, press one now.
什么叫做
What exactly does that expression mean,
"互利友人"
"friends with benefits"?
他给她提供健康保障了?
Does he provide her with health insurance?
不是
No.
想象你和某人 保持性交关系
Imagine you maintained a friendship with someone you had sex with,
但同时能和任何人约会
but you were free to date whoever you wanted.
抱歉  我想不出任何一个
I'm sorry. I can't imagine any of that.
还是玩游戏吧
All right. Back to the game.
应该轮到我了
I believe it's my turn.
你们随时可以提问了
You may begin your questions whenever you're ready.
你是斯波克吧[星战人物]
Are you Spock?
我不喜欢这个游戏
I don't like this game.
轮到谁了
So, where were we?
你不是应招去做爱吗
Aren't you leaving for your booty call?
不是  是其他事
No, it was something else.
怎么什么事都要和性爱挂钩  拜托
Why does everything have to be about sex with you? Come on.
轮到谁了
Whose turn is it?
到你了
We were up to you.
好  开始吧
Great. Just start.
好
Okay, let's see.
你是连续剧里的吗
Are you from a TV series?
她把我甩了
She dumped me!
我看他是《巴比伦5号》的
I bet he's someone from Babylon 5.
我们猜不中了
We're never going to get it.
本字幕由 YYeTs人人影视 翻译制作
更多美剧下载 请登陆 www.YYeTs.net
莱斯利怎么了  为什么甩你
What happened with Leslie? Why did she dump you?
我不知道  她就说
I don't know. She just said,
霍华德  老娘见异思迁了
"Howard, Mama's a rolling stone."
然后电话哔了一声就挂了
Then her call waiting beeped and she was gone.
我不明白
I don't understand.
如果你们之间没有感情
If you were in a non-emotional relationship, then why
怎么情绪反应得这么波动
are you having what appears to be an emotional response?
谢尔顿  他显然对她有感情
Sheldon, he obviously had feelings for her.
我当然对她有感情
Of course I had feelings for her.
我看了她的裸体呢  老天
I saw her naked, for God's sake.
你要转移一下注意力
Okay, look, you just need to get your mind off it.
想不想去漫画书店
Do you want to go to the comic book store?
或者看部电影
Maybe go see a movie?
我哪也不想去
I don't want to go anywhere.
我发现内华达州有一大堆
I'm given to understand that there's an entire city in Nevada
特别设计的城市能帮霍华德这类人
designed specifically to help people like Howard
忘却他们的烦恼
forget their problems.
直接用新烦恼替代
They can replace them with new problems such as alcoholism,
比如酗酒  赌博  性传播疾病
gambling addiction, and sexually transmitted diseases.
是我想错了  还是谢尔顿在说去维加斯
Is it me, or was that Sheldon's way of saying, "Vegas, baby!"?
我没去过那儿  你呢
I've never been there. Have you?
我也没有
Me? No.
我引用文森·沃恩在《摇摆者》里的话而已
I just got "Vegas, baby!" from Vince Vaughn in Swingers.
应该不错啊  反正现在周末也空下来了
It could be fun. I know my weekend's wide open, now that...
就这么办  我们去维加斯吧
Okay, let's do this. Let's go to Las Vegas.
-现在就去吗  -何乐而不为呢
- Now? Right now? - Why not?
大家都做即兴的事
People do things "right now," all the time.
我们也即兴一把
Why can't we be "right now" people, too?
回家收拾行李  我们就是即兴一族了
Go home, pack a bag, and we'll be "right now" people.
但是 我得先去药店买药
I mean, I have to stop at the drug store to refill a prescription,
买完药  我们就即兴去
but after that, we'll go right now.
你意下如何  霍华德
What do you say, Howard?
我觉得
I say...
去维加斯吧
"Vegas, baby!"
你怎么跟你妈说
What are you going to tell your mother?
我去海洋世界
"Sea World, baby!"
谢尔顿  你去吗
Hey, Sheldon, are you coming?
即使让丽蝇在我耳道里
I'd rather have a blowfly lay eggs
产卵孵幼虫  我也不去
and hatch larvae in my auditory canal.
行  我们会给你带T恤
Great. We'll bring you back a t-shirt.
谢谢
Thank you.
你好啊  邻居
Hello, neighbor.
你好  谢尔顿
Hello, Sheldon.
这个美好的夜晚过得愉快么
And how are you this fine evening?
愉快
Great.
很好  真高兴
Good. I'm glad.
是吗
Really?
你喝醉了?
Are you drunk?
我就是心情好嘛
I'm just in a good mood.
我的同胞们都去维加斯了
While my compatriots are in Las Vegas,
我就能在这美好的夜晚 独自享受《孤独要塞》了
I will be enjoying a blissful evening in my personal Fortress of Solitude.
你指的是超人的那个大冰冻那啥对吧
That's Superman's big ice thingy, right?
我现在心情好
You know, I'm in such a good mood,
居然觉得你对英语词汇掌握之贫乏
I'm actually finding your tenuous grasp
甚至有一点可爱的说
of the English language folksy and charming today.
什么闻着这么香
Mmm. What smells so good?
这是奶油咖喱的醉人香气
That is the intoxicating aroma of Kadhai Paneer,
更是对这个自由的傍晚
a perfect culinary representation
通过美食的完美体现
of the freedom this evening holds.
这不光是库萨帕里所厌恶的印度美食
Not only is it Indian cuisine, which Koothrappali loathes,
并且有大量花生作为配菜
it contains a generous helping of peanuts,
能把沃罗威茨变成一个97磅的呼哧呼哧的大泡泡
which would reduce Wolowitz to a wheezing 97-pound blister.
还有  主料是干酪  一种农家芝士
And finally, its main ingredient is paneer, a farmer's cheese
莱纳德食用后会瞬间让同房间的人
that would cause Leonard to render any room uninhabitable
死不见血
within minutes.
好吃啊
Yum.
那就祝你晚上玩得开心
Well, enjoy your big evening.
佩妮
Penny.
我知道你今晚也是一个人
I realize you're also on your own tonight,
如果你万一觉得一个人无聊了
so if, at some point, you find yourself with nothing to do,
请不要来打扰我
please do not disturb me.
谢尔顿  玩得开心
Have fun, Sheldon.
当然会了
Oh, I shall.
不要啊
No!
超人同志  您怎么了
What's wrong, Superman?
被锁在你的大冰冻那啥外面了么
Locked out of your big ice thingy?
快看
Look at this.
漱口水  润肤露  沐浴液
Mouthwash, lotion, body wash.
洗发水护发素
Shampoo and conditioner
全部在一个小瓶子里
together in one tiny bottle.
我爱拉斯维加斯
I love Las Vegas.
霍华德  能借我你的须后水用用么
Howard, could I borrow some aftershave?
黑色的包里  上面那层
Black case, top compartment.
这么多古龙水
That's a lot of cologne.
第一排是你要的麝香型
First row are your musks. Second is woods,
第二排是木头 皮革和植物味
leathers and botanicals.
第三排是配套的外激素  慎用
Third is assorted pheromones. Tread lightly.
霍华德  精神可嘉
That's the spirit, Howard.
我们能行
Yes, we can.
我们走吧
Come on. Let's go.
你们先去  我还有封邮件要回
You guys go ahead. I just have to finish up an email.
才不是邮件呢  你在看莱斯利的FACEBOOK主页
That's not an email. That's Leslie's Facebook page.
好吧
Okay, fine.
我是在看她的主页
I'm checking her Facebook page.
你看她的状态更新了  她说她把我甩了
Look at her status update. She's saying she dumped me.
大家需要知道是我甩了她
People need to know I dumped her.
事实是她甩你啊
But she did dump you.
拉杰  醒醒吧  互联网上无事实
Grow up, Raj. There's no place for truth on the Internet.
你们先去吧  我等下就去找你们
Just go. I'll catch up with you.
好吧
All right.
我们该计划一下  万一我们走桃花运呢
Oh, we should have a plan in case one of us gets lucky.
如果我走运了  我就带她
Okay, uh, if I get lucky, I'll take her
去我在哥谭城外的古堡[蝙蝠侠居住的城市]
to my stately manner outside Gotham City, and...
如果你走运了  我就去月亮上睡
if you get lucky, I'll sleep on the moon.
计划不错
Sounds like a plan.
等着  我记得备用钥匙就放在这附近
Hang on. I think the emergency key is around here somewhere.
我们有个碗
We have a bowl.
钥匙都放那个碗里
Our keys go in a bowl.
你应该弄个碗
You should get a bowl.
那么请问美丽心灵的谢尔顿·库珀
So, how did the beautiful mind of Sheldon Cooper
是怎么忘带钥匙的
forget his key in the first place?
我把它们落在碗里了
I left them in the bowl.
我想起来备用钥匙在哪了
I just remembered where the emergency key is.
-在哪  -在你们家
- Where? - In your apartment.
怎么在我们家
What's it doing in my apartment?
我几周前去过
Well, I went in there a few weeks ago,
你们不在家  被我落在那了
and you guys weren't home and I forgot it there.
你进了我...为什么
You went in my... Why would...
你说什么呢
What are you saying?
没什么大不了的
It's not a big deal. I was making
我泡咖啡的时候没牛奶了
coffee and I ran out of milk.
你就是那个偷奶贼啊
You're the milk thief!
莱纳德说我疯了 但我知道牛奶盒是轻了一些
Leonard said I was crazy, but I knew that carton felt lighter.
好啦  谢尔顿  淡定
All right. Sheldon, look. Just calm down.
我给公寓管理员打电话  叫他来开门
I will call the building manager and he'll come open your door.
你可以一边等  一边吃饭
You just eat your dinner here while you're waiting.
吃?  我的晚饭?  在你家?
Eat? My dinner? In your apartment?
是啊  怎么了
Yeah. Why not?
Sure. Why not?
日落之后  我们再坐着我的小皮卡
And after the sun's down, we can all pile in my pickup
去小溪边裸泳多好
and go skinny-dipping down at the crick.
因为今天是失去理智的日子
Cause today is the day to stop making sense.
谢谢
Thanks.
告诉你  莱纳德  老虎机
I'm telling you, Leonard... video slots...
大胸吧台妹端来的免费饮料
free drinks brought to us by a bosomy barmaid
只要三块九毛五的鲜虾自助
and all you can eat shrimp for $3.95.
迪斯尼一边去吧
Disneyland can suck it.
这里真是人间仙境
This is the real happiest place on earth.
哥们快看
Dude, check it out!
还有整月的洗衣钱
That's laundry for a month!
你好
Hello.
你叫什么
What's your name?
拉杰·罗摩衍那·库萨帕里
Rajesh Ramayan Koothrappali.
你好  拉杰拉杰·罗...
Hello, Rajesh Ra--
嗨  拉杰
Hi, Rajesh.
我是迈克拉
I'm Michaela.
你好  迈克拉
Hello, Michaela.
你想来个小小的聚会么
So, you interested in a little party?
好啊  我喜欢聚会
Why, yes, I love to party.
聚会是我的中间名
Party is my middle name.
如果不是罗摩衍那的话
Or, it would be if it weren't Ramayan.
拉杰  我能和你说句话么
Uh, Raj, can I... can I talk to you for a moment?
莱纳德  现在不行
Not now, Leonard.
迈克拉邀请我去聚会呢
Michaela's inviting me to a party.
你最好给月亮打个电话
You better call the moon
确认一下他们有没有给你备床
and make sure they have a bed for you.
拜托  我真的有话要跟你说
Yeah. I really need to talk to you.
抱歉  我马上回来
Excuse me. I'll be right back.
不要乱跑哦
Don't go anywhere.
最好连动都不要动  保持造型哦
Don't move. Just stay the beautiful,
你就像一朵未经采摘  娇艳欲滴的美式鲜花
unspoiled American flower that you are.
伙计  你发什么神经啊
What's wrong with you, dude?
那个女人已经深深地被我的雄性激素吸引了
That woman was all up in my jammy.
好吧  我真的不想打击 你所谓的"雄性激素"
Okay. I hate to break this to you and whatever your "jammy" is,
但我可以肯定她只是个娼妓
but I'm pretty sure she's a prostitute.
什么
What?
不能吧
No...
那我换个方式解释吧
Let me put it this way:
在你的一生中  能有几个超级美女
In your entire life, how many gorgeous women
会一进酒吧就过来跟你搭讪
have walked straight up to you in a bar
还问你要不要去参加派对?
and asked if you wanted to party?
或许我可以感化她
Maybe I can save her.
或许吧  但我猜你可能会为此 付出每小时500美元的代价
Maybe, but I'm guessing it'll cost you about $500 an hour to try.
很高兴认识你 祝你的未来更加灿烂美好
It was lovely meeting you. Best of luck in your future endeavors.
随你便
Whatever.
天啊  我已经开始想她了
Oh, I miss her already.
看来霍华德不行了
Oh, Howard's losing it.
他在博客上最新的留言写着
Check out his latest Twitters.
我正处于黑洞的最底端 凝视着绝望的深渊
"I'm at the bottom of a black hole "staring into the abyss.
我的生活毫无意义  我的未来一片茫然
My life is meaningless. My future is without hope."
要不带他去看蓝人乐队吧
Why don't we take him to see the Blue Man Group?
你觉得会有用吗
You think that'd help?
"今日美国"称他们为"老少咸宜爆笑组合"
USA Today calls them "exuberant fun for the whole family."
我不知道  霍华德不是那种 通吃老少咸宜乐趣的人
I don't know. Howard isn't really the family fun kind of guy.
真可惜他没在这  见不到那个妓女
It's too bad he wasn't here for that hooker.
她绝对是他喜欢的类型  标准的妓女
She's exactly his type; a hooker.
如果给钱请她帮忙  霍华德一定能振作起来
You know, I bet if we hired her, that would cheer him up.
我坚决不同意让妓女去安抚沃罗威茨
We're not gonna get Wolowitz a hooker.
我是如此孤独  熊熊的欲火燃烧着我
"I'm so lonely and horny,
我随时会开一瓶20美元的花生酱  然后全部干掉
I may open this $20 jar of peanuts and end it all."
让她报个价  应该不会被打吧
I suppose it wouldn't hurt to get an estimate.
你今天过得好吗
So how was your day?
你想跟我聊家常吗
Are you trying to make small talk?
亲爱的  你真的不必这么做
Oh, sweetie, you really don't have to.
错  这是个惯有的习俗
No, it's the accepted convention.
你今天过得好吗
How was your day?
他们把餐厅的值班表全都打乱了
Well, uh, they shifted my schedule around at the restaurant,
所以我的时间会跟平时有点不一样
so my hours are gonna be a little differe...
抱歉  我对此一点都不感兴趣  快吃吧
I'm sorry. That's not going to interest me at all. Just eat.
你好啊  小姐
Hello again.
你们好啊
Oh, hi.
你好  如果您不忙的话
Yeah, hi. Listen, um... if you're not busy,
我们想知道你是否...
we were thinking maybe you could...
我们其实是想问...
We were wondering...
你到底是不是娼妓
...if you're really a prostitute.
你们是警察吗
You guys cops?
当然不是
No.
那好  我是娼妓
I'm a prostitute.
太好了
Okay, great.
事情是这样的  我们有个朋友
Uh, the thing is, we've got this friend,
他被甩了  很沮丧
and he's kind of down in the dumps.
我们觉得你可以让他振作起来
And we thought maybe you could cheer him up.
用你的床上功夫
With sex.
不用说的这么直白吧
I think she knows what I meant.
你在那兜来兜去她怎么可能明白
How can she when you beat around the bush?
她可是红灯区的
She's from the mean streets
那里的人都是二话不说直接干正事的
where they shoot from the hip and keep it real.
放心吧  我会好好照顾你们的朋友
Don't worry. I can take good care of your friend.
好的  太棒了
Okay, terrific.
那请问能不能不让他
Uh, um... listen, is there a way that we can do this
知道你的真实身份是...
where he doesn't know that you're a, you know...
娼妓
Prostitute.
你们想要女友式的服务啊
You want the girlfriend experience.
对  对  正是
Yes. Yeah, exactly.
女友式的服务
The girlfriend experience.
其实  能不能再问一下
Actually, if it's not too much to ask,
能不能搞成犹太人式的女友服务
could we have the Jewish girlfriend experience?
这是第20个问题了
Okay, that's question 20.
你接着猜
You have to guess.
谢尔顿  放过我吧
I don't know, Sheldon.
你是《星球大战》吗
Are you Star Wars?
一个人怎么可能变身成一部电影呢
How can one person be a whole movie?
我放弃了  能不能找点别的事干
Okay, I give up. Can we just do something else?
好吧
Fine.
其实人家是斯波克啦
I was Spock.
你和莱纳德是"互利友人"吗
Are you and Leonard friends with benefits?
什么
What?
你和莱纳德是"互利友人"吗
Are you and Leonard friends with benefits?
这是谁无中生有的
Where did that even come from?
是他说的吗
Did he say we were?
不  莱纳德什么都没说
No, Leonard said nothing.
但他假装说你的信寄错了
But who knows what goes on over here
谁知道你们到底在搞什么
when he pretends your mail was misdelivered?
只是寄信  没有其他
Just mail, no benefits.
我明白了
I see.
你为什么问这个
Why are you asking?
我对于整个交际圈很是好奇
I'm curious about the whole social construct.
表面上看来 关于满足个人性欲方面
On its face, the idea of satisfying one's sexual appetite--
假设某人受到这方面的折磨
assuming one is afflicted with such--
没有感情上的纠葛 这看似相当具有实用性
without emotional entanglement, that seems eminently practical.
不过  据我观察 霍华德·沃罗维茨却是 哭得像个小女孩一样
What I've observed, however, is Howard Wolowitz crying like a little girl.
有些人只是无法处理好 那种关系而已
Well, some people just can't handle that kind of relationship.
你能么
Can you?
什么
Excuse me?
你能否做到跟一个与自己
Are you able to have sex with men
毫无情感依恋的男人上床呢
without developing an emotional attachment?
谢尔顿  我实在不想跟你讨论这个话题
Sheldon, I really don't want to talk about this with you.
这个话题让你感到不适了吗
Is this conversation making you uncomfortable?
当然了  我很不爽  看不出来吗
Of course it's making me uncomfortable. Can't you tell?
我看不出来
I really have no idea.
我实在不擅长解读
I don't particularly excel
脸部表情和肢体语言
at reading facial expressions, body language...
我要发飙了  谢同学
I'm uncomfortable, Sheldon!
谢谢  我了解了
Thank you. That's very helpful.
好啦  极品虾仁在哪儿呢
All right, where are these amazing shrimp?
看
Behold.
说真的  你觉得这有婴儿手臂大吗
Seriously, you think this is the size of a baby's arm?
迷你婴儿
A little baby.
我回房间了
Okay, I'm going back to the room.
天啊  上一盘上等"胸肉" 他们会死么!
Boy, would it maybe kill them to put out a nice brisket?
你好  我叫霍华德·沃罗维茨
Hi, there. Howard Wolowitz.
我叫埃斯特·罗森布拉特
Esther Rosenblatt.
看来管理员今晚不来了  给你
I don't think the manager's coming tonight, so here.
你准备让我睡沙发么
Are you suggesting I sleep on the couch?
我起初不这么想
Well, it wasn't the first suggestion that came to mind,
但现在就这么定
but it's the one I'm going with.
我不能睡沙发  我是睡床的
I can't sleep on your couch. I sleep in a bed.
你看看这尺寸
And given its dimensions,
我可不想成为EM斯尼科林畅销儿童书
I have no intention of living out E.M. Snickering's
《康沃尔巨人》的真人版
beloved children's book, The Tall Man From Cornwall.
你说啥
What?
康沃尔巨人
"There was a tall man from Cornwall
身高超过床
"whose length exceeded his bed.
身子躺不平
"My body fits on it, but barely upon it,
大头容不下
there's no room for my big Cornish head."
我让你睡我的床  但有一个条件
All right, I will give you my bed on one condition:
你得在接下来8小时内闭上嘴
that you promise to zip your hole for the next eight hours.
我能说最后一句话吗
May I say one last thing?
只要不押韵就成
Only if it doesn't rhyme.
好啊
All right.
晚安
Good night.
前戏么  我想想
Turn-ons? Let me see.
在火堆前读一本好书
Reading a good book in front of the fire,
沿着海滩漫步
long walks on the beach...
还有带着培根汉堡
and getting freaky on the Sabbath
在安息日[犹太人新年]狂欢
with a bacon cheeseburger.
真的吗  我也是
Really? Me, too!
哎呦喂  你好性感呐
Oy,gevalt,  you're hot.
确实
Yeah.
失陪一下下
Excuse me for a moment.
怎么样了
Hey, how's it going?
少废话  都是你一手安排的吧
Cut the crap. You set this up, didn't you?
对
Yes.
她是妓女  对吧
She's a hooker, isn't she?
对  娼妓
A prostitute, yes.
你已经付钱给她了?
You already gave her the money?
是
Yes.
太谢谢你了
Thank you!
佩妮
Penny?
咋了
What?
我睡不着
I can't sleep.
可能是因为你的嘴巴没闭上
Maybe that's because your hole is still open.
我想家了
I'm homesick.
你的家离这就20英尺
Your home is 20 feet from here.
20英尺  20光年  都没关系
20 feet, 20 light-years, it doesn't matter.
它就像在一个遥远的星系
It's in a galaxy far, far away.
妈的
Damn it.
你要我干嘛
What do you want me to do?
唱"乖乖猫"
Sing "Soft Kitty."
那是你病了才有的事
That's only for when you're sick.
想家也是一种病嘛
Homesick is a type of being sick.
拜托  非唱不可吗
Come on, do I really have to?
那就聊天吧
I suppose we can stay up and talk.
乖猫猫  暖猫猫
* Soft kitty, warm kitty *
小小毛绒球
* Little ball of fur *
快乐猫猫
* Happy kitty... *
瞌睡猫猫
Sleepy kitty.
-瞌睡猫猫  -不对
- * Sleepy kit... *  - No.
重来
Start over.
乖猫猫  暖猫猫
* Soft kitty, warm kitty *
小小毛绒球
* Little ball of fur *
快乐猫猫  瞌睡猫猫
* Happy kitty, sleepy kitty *
呜  呜  呜 [猫的叫声]
* Purr, purr, purr. *
佩妮
Penny?
怎么了
Yeah?
谢谢你让我住这
Thank you for letting me stay here.
不客气  甜心
Oh. You're welcome, sweetie.
行了  我有睡意了  出去吧
Okay, I'm sleepy now，get out.
太好了
Oh, good.
你终于回家了
You're finally home.
你在佩妮家搞什么
What were you doing at Penny's?
我们一起吃了晚餐
Well, we had dinner,
玩了些游戏  还睡了一晚
uh, played some games, and then I spent the night.
你应该很高兴  因为我终于
You'll be happy to know that I now have
对"互利友人"有更深的理解了
a much better understanding of "friends with benefits."